Taimoor Hassan

Frontend developer with 2 years of experience. I am dedicated to creating user-friendly and visually appealing websites and applications. In addition, I constantly strive to stay updated with the latest industry trends and technologies to deliver the best user experience.

Rawalpindi, PK

+923471246462

tamoorshah462@gmail.com https://github.com/Taimoor462 https://taimoor462.github.io/My-Po rtfolio/

EXPERIENCE

BCDApps, Rawalpindi — Frontend Developer

June 2022 - PRESENT

- We utilized tools like React.js, Tailwind, and Bootstrap to create seamless user interfaces.
- I used SendGrid to make email templates attractive.
- We collaborated effectively using Git version control.
- I have a strong focus on writing clean and efficient code.
- I am contributing to the creation of impactful web solutions.
- I have utilized the following skills at this platform.

Skills: ·HTML5 ·Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · JavaScript · React js · Next js · Responsive Web Design · Git · Github · SASS · LESS · Progressive Web Applications (PWAs) · Tailwind CSS · Bootstrap · Web Development · SendGrid · Typescript

Ladejavu, Rawalpindi — Intern Frontend developer

March 2022 - May 2022

- I started my 1st internship at this company as an intern frontend developer.
- I have polished my skills in HTML and CSS here.
- Also, I learned the basics of Javascript and started making templates with these skills.

Skills: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Javascript(Basics)

PROJECTS

Inresi:

https://inresi-dev.superbrightapis.net/embed/asteras?number=306&theme=light

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript / ES6, React js, Next js, Typescript, SCSS / LESS, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Git / Github, SendGrid, Responsive Design, SPA(Single Page Application)

LANGUAGES

English, Urdu, Punjabi

EDUCATION

Govt. Degree College, M.B.Din — *ICS*

Feb 2016 -Jul 2018

Unihub: https://unihub.vercel.app/

Elevate_API: https://elevate-api-lu1a.vercel.app/api-hub